David Garza

SUMMARY

Qualified and experienced geoscientist in interpretative software and research capabilities. I have worked 3 years at Welder Exploration & Production that primarily produced from dated oil & gas fields for future exploitation. Using SMT/Kingdom suites and gathered wellbore research I have evaluated and assisted in selecting prospects, running operations, conducting field work, and processing data. Skills included are:

Microsoft Word, Excel,	SMT/Kingdom	NodeJS, NPM
Powerpoint, Access	SQL Database (Access)	ArcMap (GIS)
CAD (Vizio)	HTML5/CSS/Javascript	Field work

EDUCATION

Associate of Science: Biology 2012, South Texas College, Weslaco Texas Bachelor of Science Geology 2015, University of Texas at San Antonio

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Welder Exploration & Production: November 2015 – November 2018

Geologist

- Managed part-time engineering & geological interns. Reviewed resumes, screened applicants, assigned and assisted well plannings, and subsurface field evaluations. Overlooked projects and performed intern assessments at end of program.
- Conducted wellbore research on entire oil fields. Processed and recorded regulatory documents for complete well histories. Ordered whole logs for formation tops and correlation. Utilized website data repositories for wellbore production and allocations.
- Conducted field work for facilities evaluation and process flow diagram construction on CAD softwares (Vizio). Traveled with gauger personal to areas of interest and conducted inventory of well site equipment and pipeline layout and sizes.
- Processed, digitized, and evaluated well logs for IHS/SMT Kingdom use. Edited formation tops, marked faults, tied LAS files, identified structural and stratigraphic trends on Kingdom 2d/3d seismic lines.
- Conducted reservoir analysis using past production, geological sand thicknesses, and calculated planimeter lines
- Created and utilized a relational SQL database with Microsoft access for wellbore assets, compressor, and facilities reporting.
- Managed operations meetings, noted field work to be conducted, ran cost benefit analysis and work drafts with related departments, logged and cored on drilling operations.

WORK HISTORY

Research Scientist	Texas Agrilife Extension Center	Weslaco, Texas	2010-2011
Env. Management	Department of Energy	Washington D.C	2013
Intern Geologist	Welder Exploration & Production	San Antonio, Texas	2014-2015
Geologist	Welder Exploration & Production	San Antonio, Texas	2015-2018